scoresinlive.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Statement - Privacy Policy

This statement discloses the information gathering process and the privacy and dissemination practices for the ScoresinLive.com Web site. ScoresinLive.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protect your personal privacy. 

ScoresinLive.com is a livescore portal designed to provide realtime soccer live scores and results from all soccer leagues in the world and live scores and results for all major sports as basketball, tennis, ice hockey, baseball, american football, horse racing, rugby, golf, greyhound and formula 1. 

ScoresinLive.com contains links to other web sites and ScoresinLive.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Updated 25.12.2018 

ScoresinLive.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy endeavours to describe to you our practices regarding the personal information we collect from users on our website, located at www.scoresinlive.com (the "Site"), and the services offered through the Site. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, our collection practices the processing of user information, or if you would like to report a security violation to us directly, please contact us [here](http://www.scoresinlive.com/feedback.php). 

WHAT DATA WE COLLECT 

General Data:  
The use of our services will automatically create information that will be collected. For example, when you use our Services, your geographic location, how you use the Services, information about the type of device you use, your Open Device Identification Number, date/time stamps for your visit, your unique device identifier, your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, and domain name are all collected. This information is generally used to help us deliver the most relevant information to you and administer and improve the Site. 

Log Files:  
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ("ISP"), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to maintain and improve the performance of the Services. 

Analytics:  
We use analytics services (including, but not limited to, Google Analytics) to help analyze how users use the Site. Analytics services use Cookies to collect information such as how often users visit the Site and we use the information to improve our Site and Services. The analytics services ability to use and share information collected by them is restricted by their terms of use and privacy policy, which you should refer to for more information about how these entities use this information.  
We use Google Analytics on our website, and have set the user and event data retention period to 14 months, also the IP addresses are anonymized.

This link describes how Google uses information from sites that use their services:  
<https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

Read Google's overview of privacy and safeguarding data:  
<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites:  
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

Cookies:  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information (text files) that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the website. These text files that can be used by websites to make a user's experience more efficient. 

The law states that we can store these cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of this site. For all other types of cookies we need your permission. 

To that end, this site uses different types of cookies. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages. We and some third parties may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Services and to market the Services or other products. 

Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers. This tracking is done on an anonymous basis and, while not an exhaustive list, some of the companies we work with are Google, AppNexus, Criteo, Rubicon, Pubmatic and DistrictM. 

To learn more about this practice, including the Self Regulatory Principles for Online Advertising, to which we adhere, you can visit:  
\- www.aboutads.info/choices  
\- Optout.networkadvertising.org  
\- www.youronlinechoices.com 

Location Information:  
If you have enabled location services on your mobile device, we collect your location information to make a map available to the recipients of your messages showing your location. If you do not want this information collected by us, you can disable location services on your mobile device. 

USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

In general, personal information you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, aid us in serving you better, or market our Services. We use your personal information in the following ways: 

\- Operate, maintain, and improve our site(s), products, and services;  
\- Respond to comments and questions and provide customer service;  
\- Send information including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;  
\- Communicate about promotions, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by us and our selected partners;  
\- Link or combine user information with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service;  
\- Develop, improve, and deliver marketing and advertising for the Services;  
\- Provide and deliver products and services you request;  
\- Identify you as a user in our system;  
\- Facilitate the creation of and secure your Account on our network; and 

We may store and process your personal information in servers in the United States and other countries. 

We may also create anonymous data records from your personal information by completely excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We use this anonymous data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Services and improve Site navigation. We reserve the right to use anonymous data for any purpose and disclose anonymous data to third parties in our sole discretion. 

We may receive testimonials and comments from users who have had positive experiences with our Services. We may publish such content. When we publish this content, we may identify our users by their first and last name as well as the user's title, school or company, and major. We obtain the user's consent prior to posting this information along with the testimonial. We may post user feedback on the Site from time to time. We may share your feedback with your first and last name as well as the user's title, school or company, and major. If we choose to post such information along with your feedback, we will obtain your consent prior to posting you name with your feedback. 

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We disclose your personal information as described below and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. 

Third Parties Designated by You:  
When you use the Services, the personal information you provide will be shared with the third parties that you authorize to receive such information. 

Third Party Service Providers:  
We may share your personal information with third party service providers to: provide you with the Services that we offer you through our Services; conduct quality assurance testing; facilitate creation of accounts; to provide technical support; market the Services; and/or to provide other services to us. 

Information You Share:  
Our Site and Services allow you to share content and information. Please be mindful of your own privacy needs as you choose who to connect with and what to share and make public. We cannot control the privacy or security of information you choose to make public on the Site. If you share information about others, we suggest you get consent for any information you may share about them. 

Information We Share:  
We may disclose aggregated information about our users and information that does not identify any individual without restriction. In addition, we may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide:  
\- To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it, for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information, or with your consent;  
\- To third parties designated by you;  
\- With our subsidiaries and affiliates;  
\- To third parties to process payments made through the Services;  
\- With contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business;  
\- With a Social Networking Site (SNS) if you choose to post content to an SNS through the Service;  
\- To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about users is among the assets transferred; and 

Other Disclosures:  
Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal information (as described below), ScoresinLive.com may disclose Personal information if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (i) in connection with any legal investigation; (ii) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on our company; (iii) to protect or defend the rights or property of ScoresinLive.com or users of the Services; and/or (iv) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or our Terms of Use. 

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES 

Our Site may contain links to third party websites. When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site, or Services and go to another site, and another entity may collect personal information or anonymous data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and are not responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of your personal information after you click on links to such outside websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website and App you visit. The links to third party websites or locations are for your convenience and do not signify our endorsement of such third parties or their products, content or websites. 

YOUR CHOICES REGARDING INFORMATION 

Choices:  
We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your personal information. We may periodically send you newsletters and emails that directly promote the use of our Services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the email you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Despite your indicated email preferences, we may send you service related communications, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy. 

Cookies:  
If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to accept cookies from our Services for any of the purposes described above, then you can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Consult your browser's technical information. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Services or all functionality of the Services. If you have any questions about how to disable or modify cookies, please let us know at the contact information provided below. 

THIRD PARTIES AND OPT-OUT 

A central contradiction possibility for different third-party suppliers in particular US-companies is also attainable under the following link: optout.networkadvertising.org But you can also opt-out separately for each company we work with. Responsible for the data collection and for the delivery of interest based-based online advertising are the following companies: 

4w Marketplace 

4w Marketplace (www.4wmarketplace.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of 4w Marketplace is 4w Marketplace srl located in Fisciano (Salerno) - 84084 in Via Giovanni Paolo II n.100. In case you would like to prevent 4w Marketplace from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.4wmarketplace.com/privacy/ 

Opt-out: http://www.youronlinechoices.com/it/le-tue-scelte 

Adform 

Adform (www.adform.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Adform is Adform located in Wildersgade 10B, 1, 1408 Copenhagen, Denmark. In case you would like to prevent Adform from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/ 

Opt-out: https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/ 

Amazon 

Amazon (https://www.aps.amazon.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Amazon publisher services is Amazon publisher services located in Washington - 410 Terry Ave. North, Seattle, WA 98109-5210. In case you would like to prevent Amazon publisher services from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496 

Opt-out: https://www.amazon.com/adprefs/ref=hp_468496_advertisingpref2 

AppNexus 

AppNexus (https://www.appnexus.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of AppNexus is AppNexus Group located in in New York - 28 W. 23rd Street, New York, New York, 10010. In case you would like to prevent Appnexus from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/privacy-policy 

Opt-out: https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices 

Conversant 

Conversant (https://www.conversantmedia.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Conversant is Conversant inc. located in in Chicago (IL) - 101 North Wacker, 23rd Floor Chicago, IL 60606. In case you would like to prevent Conversant from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy 

Opt-out: http://optout.conversantmedia.com/ 

Criteo 

Criteo (https://www.criteo.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Criteo is Criteo located in Paris - 32 Rue Blanche - 75009 Paris - France. In case you would like to prevent Criteo from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.criteo.com/privacy/ 

Opt-out: https://www.criteo.com/privacy/ 

District M 

District M (https://districtm.net) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of District M is District M located in Montreal - 5455 Gaspe Ave #730, Montreal, QC H2T 3B3, Canada. In case you would like to prevent District M from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://districtm.net/en/page/platforms-data-and-privacy-policy/ 

Opt-out: https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html 

Doubleclick 

Doubleclick (www.doubleclickbygoogle.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Doubleclick is Google located in Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow St Dublin 4 Ireland. In case you would like to prevent Doubleclick from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ 

Opt-out: https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en 

Facebook 

Facebook (www.facebook.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Facebook is Facebook Inc., located in 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. In case you would like to prevent Facebook from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy 

Opt-out: www.facebook.com/ads/preferences 

Indexexchange 

Indexexchange (www.indexexchange.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Indexexchange is Indexexchange located in New York - 20 W 22nd St. Suite 1101, New York, NY 10010. In case you would like to prevent Indexexchange from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/ 

Opt-out: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/ 

Media.net 

Media.net (http://www.media.net/privacy-policy) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Media.net is Media.net Advertising Ltd. located in Dubai - 107/108, DIC Building 5, Dubai Internet City, Dubai, 215028, United Arab Emirates. In case you would like to prevent Media.net from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.media.net/privacy-policy 

Opt-out: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ 

Oath 

Oath (https://www.oath.com/) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Oath is Oath (EMEA) Limited located in Dublin - 5-7 Point Square, North Wall Quay. In case you would like to prevent Oath from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://privacy.aol.com/ 

Opt-out: https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/ie/en/optout/ 

OpenX 

OpenX (https://www.OpenX.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of OpenX is OpenX located in Pasadena - 888 E Walnut St, 2nd Floor, Pasadena CA, 91101, USA. In case you would like to prevent OpenX from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.openx.com/de_de/privacy-policy/ 

Opt-out: https://www.openx.com/legal/interest-based-advertising/ 

Pubmatic 

Pubmatic (https://www.pubmatic.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Pubmatic is Pubmatic, Inc. located in Redwood City - 305 Main Street, First Floor, Redwood City, California 94063, USA. In case you would like to prevent Pubmatic from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/ 

Opt-out: https://pubmatic.com/legal/opt-out/ 

Pulsepoint 

Pulsepoint (https://www.pulsepoint.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Pulsepoint is Pulsepoint, Inc. located in New York - 360 Madison Avenue, 14th Floor, New York, NY 10017. In case you would like to prevent Pulsepoint from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy 

Opt-out: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/ 

Reachnet 

Reachnet (https://www.reachnet.de) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Reachnet is Reachnet DE Ltd. located in Hamburg - Grindelallee 41, D-20146 Hamburg. In case you would like to prevent Reachnet from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.reachnet.de/unternehmen/agb.html 

Opt-out: https://adfarm1.adition.com/opt?m=optout&n=73 

Rubicon Project 

Rubicon Project (https://www.rubiconproject.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Rubicon Project is Rubicon Project, inc. located in Playa Vista - 12181 Bluff Creek Drive, 4th Floor, Playa Vista, CA 90094, USA. In case you would like to prevent Rubicon Project from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/ 

Opt-out: https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/ 

Primis 

Primis (https://www.primis.tech) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Primis is Primis LTD located in 622 Third avenue, McCann New York House 10017 New York City, USA. In case you would like to prevent Primis from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.primis.tech/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/primisPrivacyPolicy2018.pdf 

Opt-out: https://web.archive.org/web/20180116234711/http:/live.sekindo.com/utils/cookieOptOut.php 

Smaato 

Smaato (https://www.smaato.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Smaato is Smaato Ad Services located in Hamburg - Valentinskamp 70, Emporio, 20355 Hamburg, Germany. In case you would like to prevent Smaato from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.smaato.com/privacy/ 

Opt-out: http://www.youronlinechoices.eu 

SmartAdserver 

SmartAdserver (https://www.smartadserver.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of SmartAdserver is SmartAdserver located in Paris - 66 Rue de la Chaussée d'Antin, 75009 Paris, France. In case you would like to prevent SmartAdserver from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/ 

Opt-out: http://www.smartadserver.com/diffx/optout/IABOptout.aspx 

Sovrn 

Sovrn (https://www.sovrn.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Sovrn is Sovrn Holdings, Inc. located in Boulder - 5541 Central Avenue, Boulder, CO 80301. In case you would like to prevent Sovrn from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy-eu/ 

Opt-out: https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/15620?v=1&nt=0&nw=false 

Ströer SSP 

Ströer SSP (https://www.adscale.de) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Ströer SSP is Ströer media Deutschland GmbH located in Köln - 50999 Köln, Ströer-Allee 1. In case you would like to prevent Adscale from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.adscale.de/datenschutz 

Opt-out: ih.adscale.de/adscale-ih/oo 

Twiago 

Twiago (https://www.twiago.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Twiago is Twiago located in Köln - Gustav-Heinemann-Ufer 72b, 50968 Köln. In case you would like to prevent Twiago from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: http://www.twiago.com/datenschutz/ 

Opt-out: http://control.twiago.com/privacy.php?lang=0 

Mopub 

Mopub (https://www.mopub.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Mopub is Twitter, Inc. located in San Francisco - 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, Ca 94103. In case you would like to prevent Moppub from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/ 

Opt-out: https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/ 

Inmobi 

Inmobi (https://www.inmobi.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Inmobi is Inmobi Pte Ltd located in Bangalore - Embassy Tech Square, Kadubeesanahalli Village Outer Ring Road, Varthur Hobli, Bangalore 560103. In case you would like to prevent Inmobi from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future. 

Privacy policy: https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy/ 

Opt-out: https://www.inmobi.com/page/opt-out/ 

A NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN 

Our Services are not directed to children under the age of 13 and children under the age of 13 are not eligible to use our Services. If a child under 13 submits personal information to us and we learn that the personal information is the personal information of a child under 13, we will take steps to remove the personal information from our databases. If you believe that we might have any personal information from a child under 13, please contact us [here](http://www.scoresinlive.com/feedback.php). 

YOUR RIGHTS 

As a user of our site you have the following rights:  
\- The right to ask what personal data that we hold about you at any time. Extra requests (particularly repetitive) for data may result in a fee being charged to the user.  
\- The right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal data that we hold about you free of charge.  
\- As set out above, the right to opt out of any marketing communications that we may send you. 

Further information regarding your rights can be found under:  
https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/ 

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please contact us using the contact us form [here](http://www.scoresinlive.com/feedback.php). 

MODIFICATIONS AND CONTACT 

We will, on occasion need to adapt these statements. For instance, if we modify our website or if the rules governing cookies or privacy change. We or our partners may always modify the content of the statements and the cookies that are stated without prior warning. Please refer back to this web page to see the latest version. 

In case you have any questions and/or comments, or wish to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail [here](http://www.scoresinlive.com/feedback.php).
